Okay. Amy told you some exciting news
and you acted Iike it was no big deal.
(Sheldon:)Her news sounded important,
but what you're forgetting is...
(Sheldon:)...it was an achievement
in the field of biology.
(Sheldon:)That's all about yucky squishy things.
All right, honey, she's upset.
You're her boyfriend.
You have to at Ieast try to be excited
by the things she's excited by.
- What if they simply don't excite me?
- Well, just smile and think about koalas.
(Sheldon:)She'd see right through that.
We go to the zoo all the time.
(Sheldon:)She knows my koala face.
(Sheldon:)And for future reference, it's this.
Wow, you have a lot of magic stuff.
Yeah, started when I was a teenager.
(Howard:)Thought I could show a girl a few tricks
and invite her up to my bedroom...
(Howard:)...to see the rest of the act.
- Did it work?
- Let's just say...